All you need is one magic base bow with
你只需要一把带有
a prefix of increased physical damage to
增加物理伤害前缀的魔法弓就可以了
follow along. From here, we will make
。 接下来，我们将把这把
this bow into a rare with the greater
弓打造成一件稀有物品，使其具有更强的
essences of abrasion and in a flat
耐磨性和更强的
physical damage. We must remove that
物理伤害。 我们必须移除该
attribute requirements because we do not
属性要求，因为我们不
want it as a suffix. So, we must ring in
希望它作为后缀。 因此，我们必须迎接
the omen of dextral crystallization,
右旋结晶的到来，
which when active in your inventory, the
当它在你的物品栏中激活时，
perfect or corrupted essence will only
完美或腐化的精华只会
remove a suffix. So, go ahead and
移除一个后缀。 所以，赶紧
activate that and grab the perfect
激活它，获取完美的
essence of abrasion to give your weapon
磨损精华，使你的武器
damage as extra physical damage and it
伤害转化为额外的物理伤害，它
should remove the suffix unless you have
应该会移除后缀，除非你使用了
the wrong crystallization omen. Now that
错误的结晶预兆。 现在
our prefixes are done and set, we can
前缀已经完成并设置好了，我们可以开始
now work on the suffixes. For this,
处理后缀了。 为此，
we'll activate the omen of greater
我们将激活“更高
exaltation, which when activated in your
崇高的预兆”，当它在你的
inventory, your next exalted orb will
物品栏中激活时，你的下一个崇高石将
add two random modifiers.
添加两个随机词缀。
Perfect exalted orb two random
完美崇高宝珠带有两个随机
modifiers, one of them being increased
词缀，其中一个是提高
attack speed, which is really nice. Now,
攻击速度，这非常好。 现在，
we can add our last suffix. We have the
我们可以添加最后一个后缀了。 我们拥有
perfect essence of haste to give our
完美的迅捷之力，可以赋予我们的
weapon onslaught and we also have the
武器猛攻；我们也拥有
perfect essence of battle to get our
完美的战斗之力，可以提升我们
level of all attack skills. However, we
所有攻击技能的等级。 然而，我们
do not need to activate the omen of
不需要激活
dextral crystallization to remove
右旋结晶的征兆来去除
suffixes simply because these will give
后缀，因为这些后缀会给
it suffixes and you can only remove a
它添加后缀，而你只能通过去除
suffix to add a suffix. Therefore,
后缀来添加后缀。 因此，
it should remove a suffix and bam. So,
它应该删除一个后缀，然后就结束了。 所以，
what we're trying to do is have a base
我们想做的就是建立一个
with both onslaught, level of all, and a
既有猛攻、又有全面进攻、还有
desecration. Now, we can grab an omen of
亵渎效果的基地。 现在，我们可以抓住领主的预兆，
liege and also force the suffix
也可以用
desecration with the omen of dextral
右手
necromancy. The omen of liege will give
死灵术的预兆强制加上亵渎的后缀。 领主预兆会给
you attack speed, which is pretty
你提供攻击速度，这相当
decent. So, in order to do that, we can
不错。 所以，为了做到这一点，我们可以
just activate the omen of liege,
激活领主之兆，
activate the omen of dexterity
激活灵巧死灵术之兆，
necromancy and grab that Alma modifer on
并在后缀上获取阿尔玛修正
the suffix. Now, we have our desecration
。 现在，我们有了亵渎技能，
and plus three level of all attack
并且所有攻击技能都提升了三级
skills. We just need our onslaught
。 我们只需要猛攻就行了，
unless you really want leeches on your
除非你真的想让你的武器上沾满水蛭
weapon, which I do. Boom, baby.
，而我确实想。 砰，宝贝。   好了
And there we go. This is the outcome we
。 这就是我们
wanted and we can now go desecrate.
想要的结果，现在我们可以去亵渎神灵了。
Yeah, even I know the most fun you want
是啊，连我都明白你最想
to see it.
看到的是什么。
I'll show him that and let me give it a
我会让他看看，然后
quick little whip.
轻轻抽他一下。
He said it was a good looking bow, guys.
他说，伙计们，这弓箭真好看。
Reveal.
揭示。
Increased attack speed.
攻击速度提升。
And now our bow is complete. Increase
现在我们的鞠躬就完成了。 提高
the quality.
质量。
Add your sockets.
添加您的插座。
Deactivate the omens and now your
解除预兆，现在你的
obliterator bow is ready for the temple
毁灭之弓已准备好进入
of corruption. Activate every single
腐败神殿。 激活
omen of corruption in your inventory in
你物品栏中所有腐化预兆，
order to begin your chant and look for
开始吟唱，寻找
that third and juicy socket.
第三个也是最肥美的插槽。
me, Lord? Yeah, even I go ahead and get
主啊，您真的通过和我交谈就明白了吗？ 是的，我甚至可以给
you a whip.
你弄条鞭子。
Lord, it smelled so good. That's right.
天哪，闻起来真香。 这是正确的。
Wait, wait, wait. Just what about the
等等，等等，等等。 那么
second corruption?
第二起腐败事件又是怎么回事呢？
Yeah, it will definitely not go poopy
是的，这次肯定不会出什么岔子
this. You got it. Oh, baby. With even I
。 答对了。 哦，宝贝。 即使有了
blessing of fortune telling, we can now
占卜的祝福，我们现在也可以
go for our second corruption using the
使用
architect's orb, which will modify a
建筑师之球进行第二次腐化，这将
corrupted equipment even further or
进一步改变腐化的装备，或者将
completely destroy it. And with all that
其彻底摧毁。
being said, it is time for the second
说了这么多，现在是第二轮
chant.
呐喊的时候了。
&gt;&gt; Oh, new
哦，新
video.
视频。
I threw that one in there just so that
我把那个放进去，就是为了让
you can see the value of the bow
你们明白弓箭
builder's crafting bench.
制作工作台的价值。
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声]
[music]
[音乐]